[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor and director, who took the name Broncho Billy, is best-known as the first star of the Western film genre.", "correct_answer": "Max H. Aronson", "incorrect_answers": ["Tim Holt", "Tom Mix", "Charlie Chaplin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Scorpion venom is regarded as a potential source of chemicals that can be used in the treatment of this disease.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Autoimmune disorders", "Cancer", "Multiple sclerosis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1980s, who voiced the character of Dino, the pet dinosaur in the animated series The Flintstones?", "correct_answer": "Mel Blanc", "incorrect_answers": ["Frank Welker", "Jean Vander Pyl", "Alan Reed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Richard Gere became known for actively raising awareness of this crucial issue.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Human rights", "Environmental problems", "AIDS"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which musical, directed by Robert Wise, is ranked # 41 on the AFI Top 100 list?", "correct_answer": "West Side Story", "incorrect_answers": ["The Sound of Music", "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", "My Fair Lady"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1899, this  world famous institution was opened in The Bronx.", "correct_answer": "The Bronx Zoo", "incorrect_answers": ["Columbia University", "The U.S. Olympic Hall of Fame", "The American Hall of Fame"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2002, which phone manufacturer announced the first handset with camera for cdma2000 1x EV-DO service?", "correct_answer": "LG", "incorrect_answers": ["Motorola", "Nokia", "Sony Ericsson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do you call a massive system of stars held together by gravity?", "correct_answer": "A galaxy", "incorrect_answers": ["A nebula", "None of these", "Space"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is written on Chad Danforths shirt in the movie High School Musical?", "correct_answer": "I come with my own background music", "incorrect_answers": ["I make my own background music", "I make cool background music", "I come with cool background music"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Wedding Crashers, Owen Wilsons character falls in love with Claire Cleary. He later gets introduced to William Cleary, played by Christopher Walken. What is William Clearys profession?", "correct_answer": "U.S. Treasury Secretary", "incorrect_answers": ["U.S. National Security", "U.S. Minister of State", "U.S. General Marshall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sublimation means channeling an urge in another direction.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is NOT the name of one of the Dread Pirate Roberts in the movie The Princess Bride?", "correct_answer": "Johann", "incorrect_answers": ["Ryan", "Westley", "Cummerbund"]}]